ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Union Health Center. Tax shelter annuity plan with Hartford Life Insurance Company., 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  9/74-4/75.
- Union Health Center. Union Label department., 1964-1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  2/64-9/72. Construction in 275 7th Avenue.
- Union Health Center. Vault tax exemption., 1973 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  5/73-9/73.
- Union Health Center. X-ray and miscellaneous equipment., 1952-1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  4/52-7/75.
- Unity House. "A" building correspondence., 1973-1976 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  7/73-2/76. Includes alterations and installations.
- Unity House. American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP). Agreements and correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1979 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  5/54-6/79.
- Unity House. American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP). Agreements and correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1979 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Unity House. Condemnation of property due to construction of roads., 1961-1972 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  8/61-6/72.
- Unity House. Copyright problems., 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  7/74-10/75. Involves mural in hotel. [Related photographs can be found in photo collection -Unity House - Caricature Mural.]
- Unity House. Corporation law file., 1969-1976 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  1/69-12/76. Includes conversion to non-profit status.
- Unity House. Damages to facilities., 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  1/70-3/73.
- Unity House. Damages to facilities., 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  4/73-8/75.
- Unity House. Damages to facilities., 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  8/75-4/76.
- Unity House. Damages to facilities., 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  6/76-7/77.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1928-1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  12/28-12/61. Includes correspondence about corporate status, capital valuation and assessment, income statements, balance sheets, and debt.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1962-1964 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  8/62-7/64.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1964 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  7/64-12/64.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1965 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  1/65-3/65.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1965-19/6 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  4/65-12/67.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1968-1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  1/68-2/71.
- Unity House. Income tax audits., 1971-1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  5/71-5/76.
- Unity House. Kitchen and dining room alterations., 1968 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  1/68-11/68.
- Unity House. Kitchen and dining room alterations., 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  12/68-1/69.
- Unity House. Kitchen and dining room alterations., 1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Unity House. Land title disputes., 1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  4/75.
- Unity House. Light and power supply., 1956-1970 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  5/56-6/70. Agreements and correspondence.
- Unity House. Liquor license renewals. Correspondence., 1953-1960 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  5/53-6/60.
- Unity House. Liquor license renewals. Correspondence., 1961-1969 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  5/61-1/69.
- Unity House. Liquor license renewals. Correspondence., 1969-1973 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  5/69-6/73.
- Unity House. Liquor license renewals. Correspondence., 1973-1979 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  7/73-6/79.
- Unity House. Operational assessments (Notice of increase)., 1975 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  12/75.
- Unity House. Promotional materials., 1960-1967 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  3/60-8/67.
- Unity House. Property (stock) transfers., 1934-1975 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  12/34-7/75.
- Unity House. Proposed construction of dining room, kitchen, administration building, and boilers., 1958-1969 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  10/58- 9/69.
- Unity House. Proposed construction of dining room, kitchen, administration building, and boilers., 1969 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  9/69-12/69.
- Unity House. Publicity pamphlet. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Unity House. "R" building alteration of 24 rooms., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  8/74.
- Unity House. Retirement benefits for employees., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  8/73-11/74.
- Unity House. Sewage treatment facility., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  10/73-8/74. Proposed joint project with Tamiment, Inc.
- Unity House. Sewage and water problems., 1950-1957 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  8/50-2/57.
- Unity House. Sprinkler system installation and alteration., 1961-1964 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  4/61-7/64.
- Unity House. Sprinkler system installation and alteration., 1964 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  9/64.
- Unity House. Sprinkler system installation and alteration., 1964-1970 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  9/64-9/70.
- Unity House. Tamiment, Inc. property swap., 1973-1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  5/73-6/73.
- Unity House. Union matters. General correspondence., 1955-1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  7/55-10/76.
- Unity House. Union matters. American Guild of Variety Artists., 1970 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  7/70-10/70.
- Unity House. Union matters. Contracts., 1959-1976 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  Includes 1959, 1964, 1965, 1967, 1970, 1973, and 1976.
- Unity House. Union matters. Employee problems., 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  4/67-4/68.
- Unity House. Union matters. Negotiations., 1964-1970 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  7/64-2/70.
- Unity House. Value and real estate assessment., 1957-1975 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  2/57-10/75.
- Miscellaneous articles. (Box 45, Folder 16)
- F. Miscellaneous Materials (Box 45, Folder 16a)
- Agreements, 1919-1935 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association (1919, 1929, 1935), Industrial Council of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association (1924, 1926, 1929, 1935), Merchants' Ladies Garment Association (1935), and others.
- Agreements, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Merchants' Ladies Garment Association, Infants' and Children's Coat Association, American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, National Skirt Manufacturers' Association, and others.
- Agreements, 1937-1964 (Box 45, Folder 18a)
  Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Merchants' Ladies Garment Association, American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, Infants' and Children's Coat Association. 1937, 1943, 1948, 1951, 1954, 1959, 1961, and others. 8 bound volumes.
- Appeal Committee, Rosario - 4/8/76, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Appeal Committee - Rosario: 4/8/76, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Rosario tapes - 3d Trial Committee exists of 1/8/76, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Rosario tape - 5/21/75 - trial #1, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Rosario tape - 5/21/75, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Rosario Appeal Committee - 4/8/76, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)